
 {
    "results": [
     
      {
            
     
    
    "question": "Which of the following is the biggest of all?",
    "correct_answer": "D) Universe",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) Galaxies",
        "B) Milky way",
        "C) Sun"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "The universe started ……………… ago.",
    "correct_answer": "B) 13.7 billion years",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) 18.7 billion years",
        "C) 16.7 billion years",
        "D) 15.7 billion years"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "……………… is the path of the earth around the sun.",
    "correct_answer": "B) The orbit",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) The axis",
        "C) The tract",
        "D) The milky way"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "Earth travels around the sun at a speed of …………….. per hour.",
    "correct_answer": "A) 1,07,200 kms",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "B) 6,200 kms",
        "C) 152 millions kms",
        "D) 1,02,700 kms"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "Earth takes ………………. days to complete one revolution.",
    "correct_answer": "D) 3651/4 days",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) 28 days",
        "B) 30 days",
        "C) 366 days"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "Which of the following causes seasons on the earth?",
    "correct_answer": "D) Tilt of Earth’s axis of rotation to its orbital plane",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) Daily rotation of the earth on its axis",
        "B) Monthly movement of the Moon around the Earth",
        "C) Revolution of the Earth around the Sun"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "The Earth began to form around years ago.",
    "correct_answer": "C) 412 billion",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) 13.7 billion",
        "B) 1,07,200",
        "D) 6 billion"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "Which of the following came into existence first?",
    "correct_answer": "D) Ocean species",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) Human beings",
        "B) Plants",
        "C) Animals"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "The radius of the earth is ………….",
    "correct_answer": "D) 6000 kms",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A) 1,07,200 kms",
        "B) 9000 kms",
        "C) 8848 kms"
    ]
},
{
    
    "question": "Top layer of the earth is called",
    "correct_answer": "A) Crust",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "B) Mantle",
        "C) Outer core",
        "D) None of these"
    ]
}
         
          
        
      
    ]
}
